Make a human friend you can trust,
and reveal to them your elfin identity.
After the 3rd of July, open Task 3.
Work with your friend on task three.
So that's your second task?
From the looks of it,
your second task is already complete.
Yep!
Does that mean you can stay?
We can go on missions together!
Not the response I expected.
Why did he ask you to team up with a human to complete it?
Can someone without experience help?
When you accepted the mission,
Did you consider the fact that Xiaobai is only in elementry?
If I can't help, Gen surely can.
There doesn't seem to be a limit on how many can help.
But we'll see later.
July 3rd is tomorrow.
Are you able to look fully human yet?
Not yet.
Well, just stay in cat form for now.
Having cat ears and white hair might draw unwanted attention.
Can't he just wear a hat?
I'd be more comfortable in my cat form.
Didn't the guild master talk about people who can change your form?
That's only visually.
Spiritual Powers
in Another World
I'd like to get better at it gradually.
I think you look cute with cat ears.
Hello?
Shanxin!
I didn't forget.
It's still too early, isn't it?
Wait, what?!
Yo!
What are you doing here?
I assumed you were in trouble.
I saw you weren't online yet.
I thought it wasn't for another hour.
I knew it...
You can get in early.
If I hadn't come, we wouldn't have been able to log in together.
Don't worry, just leave it to me.
Alright.
You didn't bring your console?
No, we can play up to four people on just one.
You should play with us, Gen!
Shanxin says it's a ton of fun.
Oh? What's it called?
All Living Creatures
Oh, that?
You've heard of it?
I've seen it around.
It seems pretty interesting.
Let's play together then.
Xiaohei, you should play too.
Me?
You guys must've been excited for this, too.
Don't you know what this game is?
Do you know how popular it is..?
How on earthly did you get the limit edition!
Forget it. Let's get straight to it.
One receiver per person. First, put it on.
It's so light, it's like a eye mask.
Then, you gotta connect to the internet.
I'm setting it up so we're all in the same lobby.
Alright, we should be ready to go at 9:30.
Who are you?!
This game is to be played in bed.
Just lie down and press this button on the side.
I'll tell you the rest after we get in.
Hello and welcome to
'All Living Creatures'.
Please state your username.
Xiaobai.
Please select your character's race.
Woah, there's so many.
Huh? Aren't these all animals?
Yes, this is a game feature of 'All Living Creatures'.
Can I change it afterwards?
Changes cannot be made unless the account is deleted.
Well, I'll stick with being human, then.
Do you want to create a new look or use your own appearance?
Use my own appearance.
Would you like to change clothes?
Nope. This works.
Huh?
A baby chick?
I'm a bird!!
Shanxin?!
Would you like to set up a subsidiary account?
This is a special option given to you
based on your unique situation.
Understood.
Welcome to 'All Living Creatures'.
Please wait in the online lobby for the game to start.
Gen!
Oh! Xiaohei!
You're finally here!
Oh? How interesting.
So cats can play, too?
This is quite the discovery.
If I had known, I would have brought Huangshou.
Wait a sec...
You both chose human. How boring.
Huh?
I don't understand what's going on.
What kind of game is this?
It's a virtual reality game.
It perfectly stimulates the senses in our brain,
to create the most realistic game ever!
This feels too real...
What's next?
Don't know.
Huh?
We won't know until the game starts.
They didn't reveal anything.
But because of this games revolutionary technology,
the game has been selling like crazy!
Launch day has obtained an incredible amount of hype.
Can't you feel it?
No...
Seems like we're in completely different worlds.
Finally, the game is about to be unveiled!
And, amazingly, you can choose to be any creature you want!
So I chose what I always wanted to be! A bird!
But flying is a lot harder than it looks.
Is this really just a game?
It's amazing. It just feels so real.
Yeah, but they nerfed any pain.
How'd they to do this?
Welcome to 'All Living Creatures'!
I am M.T., your guide for this game.
I shall now explain the basics of the game.
This is a brand new open-world game.
As you explore, you will discover more about the game and it's world.
I swear I've seen them before.
And don't forget to check our official website for any updates.
This is their company logo.
I want to go over some things before you begin.
Some pertain to the life system in the game.
I'll go over some of the basic mechanics of the game.
If a character is downed,
and is not revived within ten seconds,
That character will be deleted.
What? Deleted!?
Correct. All characters in this game are real players.
Each player gets one character.
After a character has been deleted,
the player will respawn as a new character.
The player cannot enter until after a 30-minute cooldown.
So, protect yourself just as you would in the real world.
Using a hardcore penalty...
Got it.
Um..
I'm not sure I get it...
You can bring up the user interface just by thinking "Open".
To optimize the gaming experience, your interface is visible only to your team.
If you don't have any further questions, you can mark yourself as "Ready".
Once it hits 10 o'clock, you can start the game.
Huh, no tutorial?
That's correct.
Interesting...
Try to stay together once we're in.
It's going to be crowded in the starting zone.
It's probably not going to be safe until we familiarize ourselves with the game.
We're already in each others' friends list.
So if we do get separated,
we can find each other using location tracking.
Below the our names is the experience bar.
Fill it up to level up.
Leveling up gives you skill points,
which you use to learn skills and abilities.
There's also a quest log.
Once you accept a quest, it'll show up here, but it's empty now.
There's the shop, but there isn't much in it yet.
This side is the Combat Support System.
We'll have to see what it does once we're inside.
All good?
Let's get ready to log in.
Got it!
Oh right, is there no server selection?
No, all players are on one single server.
...That's intense, so many players and no server splitting?
So... should we log in now?
Yeah, let's log in!
Are we... inside the game?
Seems like it.
Wow...
But how come there's no one here?
What's going on...?
Hm?
Shanxin, what's wrong?
New message?
"I can't speak!"
That's what makes it realistic, birds obviously can't talk
"Tired of typing!"
So annoying...
I'll try to familiarize myself with the UI for now.
Only shows up to three kilometers around us.
So we have to explore this area first?
Xiaohei, you can't read this, right? I'll read it for you.
Huh?
I see someone.
They ran off...
Probably because we're a big group.
Xiaohei.
Can you sense the presence of an elfin?
Ah, yeah!
How can there be spirits in a game?
I saw something about it on the elfin forum, so I wanted to check it out.
It's the hottest topic on the forum right now.
This is a game... For elfin.
Wow, it's exactly the same as the real world!
This is fun even all by itself!
There's over ten million people online right now.
And the number is only growing.
With that many players on the same server,
and the fact we haven't seen anyone,
this world must be enourmous.
There's no way this game could have a world chat,
the chat box would explode.
Something wrong?
I can't summon Heixiu.
Even though we can sense elfin and retain our abilities,
these bodies aren't our real bodies.
They're much weaker than in reality.
Ah!
Is this considered a monster in the game?
What do we do?!
Run!!
Shanxin!
Gen, you're amazing!
Huh?
Looks like I leveled up.
See, I'm level two.
Wasn't that your ability just now?
You can use it in the game then?
This game is connected to elfin.
Oh? No wonder, that's amazing.
But what happens if Shanxin "dies"?
Let's log out first
Okay
How do we log out?
Ah, found it, it says logout here.
Here we go.
"Are you sure you want to log out?"
It says you'll log back in at the same spot, so be careful.
Shanxin, are you okay?
That was terrifying, getting stomped to death is terrifying...
Did you guys get killed by the monster too?
No, Gen defeated it.
That's amazing! How did you do it?
Ah
That might be hard to explain...
It's a secret, can't say!
Oh, a secret, never mind then.
Doesn't saying it's a secret just makes it more intruging?
Not at all.
You don't have to tell secrets, but you can't lie about them.
Shanxin really is Xiaobai's best friend.
It's safe to fill her in on our secret, right?
Mhm! Of course
Spirits, elfins, a game for elfin... I see.
Don't be so cold to Huangshou from now on.
Are people these days really that accepting?
Anyway, Gen is still Gen!
Xiaohei is still Xiaohei, nothing's changed
Exactly!
All this really means is...
We're even stronger!!
Do you only care about the game?!
That said, the death penalty in this game is way too harsh...
I still have to wait half an hour before I can get back in.
Don't worry, we can gather intel in the meantime.
Where's Mr. Fu?
Playing the game.
Always thinking about fighting.
Suits him well.
It's rare for us to have some peace and quiet.
Exactly.
Ah!! You've got to be kidding!
I was having so much fun! Then I got ambushed!
Now I have to wait half an hour!
Seems like Mr. Fu is really enjoying the game.
When I get back in, I'm going to kick his ass!
Elfin will have an advantage at the start.
But after a while, he might not be so happy.
Isn't this game made specifically for elfin?
Hm.
That's only one of the reasons.
What!?
All living creatures in this game are played by players.
So all those animals we saw earlier were players as well.
That's so cool!
No wonder it's called All Living Beings.
Oh, so choosing a race is a feature of our limited edition.
"Turned into a strange animal randomly"
"I am a pitcher plant"
As expected of a limited edition.
Some people are talking about factions and red names.
What's that?
Characters start off belonging to the regional faction of their spawn point.
If you kill someone in you faction, your name will turn red.
However, other species aren't affected.
No ones sure what the red name does, though.
There's not much information on gameplay yet.
Most people on the forums right now are dead players, like me.
So there's limited info right now.
Hm?
"Can I earn real cash?
That's awesome"
The game has a way of earning real money?
"First, I have to reincarnate as a human."
I didn't even notice. Let's check it out later.
The rule about characters being deleted on death seems to have blown up online.
There's already a protest thread.
Woah, that's a lot of people.
I wonder if they'll end up changing it.
Absolutely not.
Oh?
Does Gen have insider info?
The elfin forum is discussing it too.
The admin clearly responded that they won't change this rule.
I never noticed before, but the moderator is actually Kali.
Oh?
A game for elfin...
Why would an elfin make a game?
To make money
With such a punishing mechanic, won't it drive away players?
It wasn't put in for the purpose of making money.
It's just to recreate the world's authenticity as much as possible.
However, with such advanced technology, it's impossible not to make money.
Since there's a player cap, I want the player quality to be higher.
Those who quit aren't the
target audience anyway.
It'll be good to filter them out.
Ah!
The official response is out!
"The rules won't change.
Limited to 50 million units."
Ah.
So blunt.
Fifty million copies, is that a lot?
Hmm..
In terms of sales,
it would rank in the top dozen or so in console history.
But no one has ever limited console sales, let alone to 50 milllion.
I wouldn't be surprised if there's even more backlash from players.
It doesn't matter, it's a seller's market.
If rules get changed just because people oppose them...
Then where's the fun in that?
No matter how high your level or how strong your abilities, one death resets everything to zero.
The more I think about it, this enhances the realism.
I've never seen an MMO do this by default.
But that makes it even more interesting...
Only the players who embrace this rule can truly enjoy the game at it's full potential.
Games are only fun when they're challenging!
I'm getting fired up!
Can't you feel the adrenaline rush?!
I can.
Alright, time's up. Let's go.
Okay.
Yo!
You aren't a bird anymore?
You can re-choose your race after death.
I want to get used to the game first.
By the way, change your outfits.
You guys look out of place.
Huh?
There's a ton of people over there!
It looks like they're fighting...
A boss?
Oh?
This game has bosses too?
Together!
No skills at all!?
How are we supposed to fight this??
How should I know
Ahhhhhhhhhhh!!!
That hurts...
Wait wait wait!!
Let's talk it out!!
You're a player too, right!?
What?! How did you become a boss?
The game randomly asks players if they want to be a boss.
It'll assign a time and location, and gives extra abilities once there.
You can move freely otherwise.
Wouldn't that cause issues?
Perhaps at first.
But once everyone gradually understands what a boss is,
I doubt it'll be a problem.
Your boss role was assigned randomly, right?
Let's make a deal!
I'll give you 2000¥ if you let me kill you. Sound good?
No way!!
That's so shameless!
This has to be an exploit!!
It's quiet today.
I got an item!!
Every game has pay-to-win players.
They paid real money without even knowing what they'd get...
Can't we just rob this guy?
Huh?
Oh, that's right. Items are usually bound or can have a low drop-rate.
However, with the current death mechanic, all items should drop.
This would make players want to fight more.
I wouldn't if I were you!
If you rob me, that'd just make you the next target.
Haha, sure is realistic.
Since we can choose races, can we choose to be a boss?
We can try next time.
Somethings not right.
Hm? What?
That guy getting robbed is getting stronger.
Hey, you're right.
Woah...
I'm... Getting stronger...
He's charging at us!
Run!
Gen, attack!
Huh?
That was intense... It really felt like I was going to die...
What item did that guy get to be so strong?
We all died this time, now we gotta wait another half hour.
This game is so hard, even Gen got taken out.
That guy probably leveled up a lot while being ganged up on.
Anyway, let's keep gathering intel.
Okay.
Xiaohei, choose human form this time.
With how the game works,
it should be easier to use your abilities.
Got it.
Ah, it got reported after all.
The game boss was bribed and dropped high-tier items.
The official response says this is part of the games experience and won't intervene.
But the boss player has been noted as a disqualified,
And they won't get another chance to become a boss.
Wow, the there's already someone who's already over level 50.
The game seems so unbalanced. How are they going to manage?
What level are we now?
Level zero...
Still, this game is pretty fun.
Time to eat!
Someone's already compiled the experience values.
Level 1 requires 1 exp, Level 2 requires 2 exp.
And so on.
Seems simple enough.
But since all experience comes from PVP,
gaining any becomes much harder.
The experience gained from killing a player isn't fixed.
You get 30% of the target's total
experience with a minimum gain of 1 exp.
At level 10 you unlock the ability "Level Eye"
which lets you see other players' levels.
It's only been two hours since launch, and there's already a 50-level gap.
Based on the experience accumulation logic,
he's essentially killed over a thousand players.
That many!?
Of course, some of those taken down
had to be high-level players.
So the actual kill count is at most a few hundred.
That's still a lot.
How did they manage that?
It's an extreme case.
Sounds like they're talking about something impressive...
They probably obtained a large AOE attack skill or possibly a weapon.
Player levels are bound to be like a pyramid.
This game has no balance at all!
The main gameplay styles seem to be:
Faction warfare,
Faction warfare, city management,
Faction warfare, city management, exploration,
Faction warfare, city management, exploration, player hunters, and anti-hunters.
How should we play then?
Let's start with just surviving.
Xiaohei, we'll be counting on you this time.
Never thought a pro gamer like me would end up so behind.
Alright! Let's get into the game!
Okay!
We're in a city this time? There's many people...
This city is way too generic. I was hoping for something original.
Now's not the time for that!
We're gonna die!!
How do we always end up running into this stuff?
What level do you need to be to get that strong?
We won't be able to see his level until we hit 10.
Right...
Wow! So fast!
So strong!!!
Huh?
What's happening?
Did they level up?
Probably a skill that only high-level players have.
So intense...
They're all so strong...
This is humilating! I've never been toyed like this in any game before.
Haha, but it's really fun though.
Next time we go in, we'll definitely have more experience.
Yeah, but I have to head back now, let's continue tomorrow.
Tomorrow won't work,
We have to go do Xiaohei's mission early tomorrow morning.
Oh?
Stay with me - let's walk on, kicking pebbles as we go
Stay with me aruite yukou ishikoro wo kette
Our destination may be whimsical
Yukisaki wa kitto kimagure demo
But with the scent of flowers in both hands
Hana no kaori wo ryoute ni
I’ll carry it to the you I’ve yet to meet
kore kara deau kimi e to
Wait for me — let’s talk, side by side
Wait for me hanashi wo shiyou kata wo narabete
Even if our first “hello” is a little awkward
Hajimemashite wa gikochinaku temo
When we open the boxes we’ve brought
Mochiyotta hako aketara
Let’s share the dreams we’ve packed inside
Tsumekon da yume wo wakeaou
The days when we can casually say “See you tomorrow”
Mata ashita tte atarimae ni kawaseru hibi ga
Are so precious and so fleeting
Itoshikute hakanasugite
Those feelings will never fade away
Omoi wa kitto kienai
We can’t catch up to the clouds drifting across the sky
Sora wo nagareru kumo ni wa oitsukenai kedo
But they’ll turn to rain, bloom into flowers
Ame ni natte hana wo tsukete kitto boku wo yonderu
And surely, they’re calling out to me
Kitto boku wo yonderu